sharetv.org 2012-05-15

# Privacy Policy - ShareTV

**¬ UPDATE:** The networks are announcing what shows are coming in the Fall. Take a look here. 

We respect your privacy and are committed to safeguarding it while online at our site **ShareTV.org**. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site. 

**Log Files**  
Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. Our site uses cookies only for storing ID information while being logged-in. Some of our business partners may also use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. 

**Links**  
This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

**Advertisers**  
We use outside ad companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies and/or web beacons to collect data in the ad serving process and are collected by our ad companies, and we do not have access to this information. We work with the ad companies: Google Adsense. Please check their websites for respective privacy policies. 

**Google AdSense**  
Google uses what's called the DART cookie, which enables it to serve ads to you based on your visits on this site and other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

**Contact Information**  
If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at: admin@sharetv.org
